pizzahut.co.uk 2009-04-21

# Pizza Hut

Pizza Hut (UK) Limited and its franchisees (hereinafter referred to as either, "Company", "We", "Us" or "Our") are committed to protecting the privacy of personal information you may provide Us on this website (the "Site") and are conscious of Our responsibilities as a 'data controller' under the Data Protection Act 1998. We believe it is important for you to know how We treat your personal information. The terms of this Privacy Policy apply to all users of this Site. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should immediately cease the use of this Site. Below you will find answers to several questions regarding Our revised Privacy Policy. 

**1\. What information does Company collect about me on this Site?**

Registration  
The Company will collect personally identifiable information that you may voluntarily provide on online forms, which may include: user registration, sweepstakes registration, contact requests, guest comments, online surveys, and other online activities. The personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") collected can include some or all of the following: your name, address, telephone number, e-mail addresses, and any other information you may voluntarily provide. At the time of registration, you will have the option to receive future offers and updates from the Company by e-mail and SMS marketing. If you choose to receive these, your Personal Information will be kept in a secured database and We will alert you via e-mail or SMS with information about Our great Pizza Hut offers and services. Customers who place online orders will also receive relevant service announcements from time to time. You can unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions contained in every email and SMS message that we send.

On-line Ordering  
If you are using Our on-line ordering site, the Company may also collect financial information including details of payment mechanisms such as your credit and debit card information and information on goods which are sold and purchased. 

Cookies  
Our Site may use technologies such as "cookies" to provide visitors with tailored information upon each visit. Cookies are a common part of many commercial websites that allow small text files to be sent by a website, accepted by a web browser and then placed on your hard drive as recognition for repeat visits to the Site. Every time you visit Our Site, Our servers, through cookies, pixels and/or GIF files, collect basic technical information such as your domain name, the address of the last URL visited prior to clicking through to the Site, and your browser and operating system. If you like, you can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie so you have the chance to accept it and you can also set your browser to turn off all cookies. The web site www.allaboutcookies.org (run by the Interactive Marketing Bureau) contains step-by-step guidance on how cookies can be switched off by users. You do not need to enable cookies to visit Our Site; however, some parts of the Site and some services may be more difficult or impossible to use if cookies are disabled. To emphasize, cookies are not linked to any Personal Information while on this Site. 

**2\. What does Company do with the information collected?**  
Company may use your Personal Information for any of the following purposes: 

(1) to administer your membership of the Site if you have registered with Us;

(2) to understand the use of the Site and make improvements; 

(3) to fulfill prizes in any competitions you may enter; 

(4) to respond to your specific requests and communications; and

(5) to conduct checks on the details you provide to us, where appropriate, if you are using credit or debit cards on our on-line ordering site to assist with fraud prevention schemes.

As a general rule the information which you supply will be processed purely for the purpose(s) for which it is supplied and collected. However, we may on occasion use and transfer your information to the third parties mentioned in this policy for the following purposes: (a) for business development; (b) market research; (c) to provide you with details of promotions, products, offers and services; (d) to share it between us and the parties mentioned above for direct marketing purposes.

**3\. With whom does Company share the information?**  
Yum! Brands, Inc. includes: KFC U.S. Properties, Inc., Taco Bell Corp., Pizza Hut, Inc., Long John Silver's, Inc., A&W Restaurants, Inc., WingStreet, LLC, and Yum Restaurants International, Inc.

Company may share Personal Information collected on this Site with any member of Yum Brands and any other future subsidiaries or affiliates or franchisees. This may include transfers to third parties in countries outside the European Economic Area. We will ensure that adequate safeguards are in place to protect your personal information.

This Privacy Policy applies if Company shares your Personal Information collected on this Site with any other Yum Brands members. If you choose to provide your Personal Information to other members of Yum Brands through their respective websites, then the respective Privacy Policies will apply. 

Company will not sell, rent, loan, transfer, or otherwise disclose any Personal Information to third parties except as set forth in this statement. Company may share Personal Information with third parties under the following circumstances: (i) in connection with a court order, government investigation, or when otherwise required by law; (ii) in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, or similar event; or (iii) working with third party data processing companies to support the Site's technical operation or execute a specific promotion or program (such as providing responses to the Guest Comments Page, conduct surveys, or maintain a database of visitor information, etc.). 

If Personal Information is shared with any third party for the purposes of executing a specific promotion or program, it will be clearly communicated to visitors that the third party will have no right to use the Personal Information for independent purposes. In support of this policy, Company will enter into written agreements with any third party receiving Personal Information requiring the third party to comply with Company's privacy policies and applicable laws. 

**4\. How can I stop receiving notices about future offers or to stop my Personal Information from being shared with third parties or from being sent outside the European Economic Area?**  
Please let us know by writing to us at the address given at the bottom of this policy. In addition, each time we send you marketing information by e-mail or SMS text messaging, we will provide an opportunity for you to unsubscribe from receiving further information from us.

**5\. How do I correct or update my Personal Information?**  
You control the accuracy of your Personal Information. If your Personal Information changes, feel free to correct, update or delete/deactivate it by writing to us at the address given at the bottom of this policy.

**6\. How does Company protect the security of my Personal Information?**  
Company uses appropriate security measures to protect all Personal Information collected in a secure, controlled environment. 

**7\. Does Company's Site link to other sites?**

Yes. This Site may contain links to other websites that may not be owned or operated by Company. Company cannot control nor is responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites. Company encourages you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to Personal Information collected on this Site.

**8\. How will Company notify me of changes to its Privacy Policy?**  
Company will post any changes to the Policy on the Site's Homepage, so visitors are always aware of any changes to what information We collect, how We use it, and under what circumstances We disclose it. If We decide to use your Personal Information in a manner different than first communicated, Company will notify users by e-mail to the e-mail addresses on record. Users will then be given a choice as to whether or not their Personal Information can be used in the new manner.

In the event that Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, another company acquires Company or its Affiliates, or Company sells a portion of its assets, your personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred and so We will share your information with the purchaser, who may then provide you with information on their products and services. 

**9\. How does Company handle children's privacy online?**  
If you are under 12, please do not use Our Site.

**10\. How do I contact the Company?**  
If you have any further questions concerning the Company's Privacy Policy and the use of your Personal Information, please contact:

Marketing Manager  
Pizza Hut (UK) Limited  
One Imperial Place  
Elstree  
Borehamwood  
Herts W06 1JN

You have a right to access the personal data We hold about you. If you wish to obtain a copy of this information, please write to Us at the address given above enclosing your postal details. A fee of no more than the statutory amount may apply.

Back to top
